Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes, 47643
  - Yeats, William Butler: (1) 8 pieces [see also Robins Papers], undated; 47684 (Box 191, Folder 35)
  - Yeats, William Butler: (2), undated; 47683 (Box 191, Folder 36)
  - Yeats, William Butler: (3) copies, undated; 47682 (Box 191, Folder 37)
  - Yendi, Ade´laide Kemble: 1 Letter, undated; 47681 (Box 191, Folder 38)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary (1823-1901): Letters, 1855-1876; 47680 (Box 191.5, Folder 1a)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary (1823-1901): 2 A.L.s[removed from The Pillars of the House; or, Under Wode, Never Rode], undated; 47679 (Box 191.5, Folder 1b)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary (1823-1901): Letters [ca. 1876-1880], 47678 (Box 191.5, Folder 2)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary (1823-1901): Letters, 1880-ca. 1890; 47677 (Box 191.5, Folder 3)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary (1823-1901): Letters, ca. 1890-1897; 47676 (Box 191.5, Folder 4)
  - Young, Andrew (1885- ): Letter, 1859; 47675 (Box 191.5, Folder 5)
  - Young, Charles Mayne (1777-1856): 3 Letters [2 undated; 1 1833], undated; 1833; 47674 (Box 191.5, Folder 6)
  - Young, Ella (1867-1956): 2 Letters, 1945-1946; 47673 (Box 191.5, Folder 7)
  - Young, F. E. Mills (Florence Ethel Mills) (1875- ): [see also Legal Size], 1919; 47672 (Box 191.5, Folder 8)
  - Young, S. Hall: 1 Letter [January 3, 1916], 47671 (Box 191.5, Folder 9a)
  - Young, Stark, undated; 47670 (Box 191.5, Folder 9b)
  - Younghusband, George: 1 Photograph; 2 Letters to Fairar, Frederick, Esq., 1929-1930; 47669 (Box 191.5, Folder 10)
  - Zaidenberg, Arthur (1903- ), undated; 47668 (Box 191.5, Folder 11a)
  - Zahn, Guglielmo, undated; 47667 (Box 191.5, Folder 11b)
  - Zangwill, Israel (1865-1926): Letters, 1892-1895; 47666 (Box 191.5, Folder 12)
  - Zangwill, Israel (1865-1926): Letters, 1895-1925; 47665 (Box 191.5, Folder 13)
  - Zucca, Mana (1894- ): 1 Letter, undated; 47664 (Box 191.5, Folder 14)
  - Wise, Leonard: [Bound MS.] Dumachas, 1690-2000; 47663 (Box 191.5.A, Folder data_value_missing_b40d77b5a2341e2bb82cb0e99644ead2)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Correspondence with Fales Library re the Collection: 3 Letters; 1 Carbon Copy of reply [see also Oversize & Proofs], undated; 47662 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Jonathan: 1 Memo [Oldenberg, Charles - June 5, 1968]; 2 Letters ["Eli"]; "Last Words" of Famous People, 47661 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Jonathan: TS. corrected for Emblems for the Little Dells, and Nooks, and Corners of Paradise: 8 pp [see proofs], 1 copy of drawing, undated; 47660 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Granta [January 19, 1963] [includes Emblems for Little Dells, and Nooks, and Corners of Paradise], 47659 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Jonathan: TS. Mahler 10 Symphonies [corrected; 42 pp.] [see also Proofs], undated; 47654 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Plastic Hydrangea People Poems [preliminary worksheets, version 1, 16 pp.], undated; 47658 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Plastic Hydrangea People Poems [preliminary worksheets, version 2, 10 pp.], undated; 47657 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Jonathan: TS. Plastic Hydrangea People Poems [with glosses by Tilson, Joe; 22 pp., 1969], 47656 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Mahler 10 Symphonies [handwritten outline of each; 41 pp.] [see also corrected Proofs], undated; 47655 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Final TS. Mahler [cover sheet; pp. numbered 55-96] [see also corrected Proofs], undated; 47653 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Jonathan: Miscellaneous quotations - some from Mahler [3 pp.], undated; 47652 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938), undated; 47651 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938): To Cargill, undated; 47650 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938), undated; 47649 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938): To Watt, Homer A. [Correspondence 1924-1930; undated]; to Chase, Harry Woodburn [Correspondence, October 30, 1935], 1924-1935; undated; 47648 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938), undated; 47647 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938), undated; 47646 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (1900-1938), undated; 47645 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified, undated; 47644 (Box 194, Folder 1)